Chastity Duhaney

Software Engineer Atlanta, GA| (678-549-0917)

<u>cduhaney1.github.io/Chas-Portfolio</u> | <u>github.com/cduhaney1</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/chastity-duhaney</u> | chastityduhaney@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Being in the Healthcare Industry for over 15 years helped prepare me to be an amazing entry level software developer by teaching me to exhibit strong communication and problem-solving skills with clients as well as co-workers. It has also taught me how to exemplify excellent customer relationship skills by being able to adapt and learn quickly in any situation.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

♦ HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, ES6, Bootstrap, Node.js, PostgreSQL, AWS, PM2, GitHub, Express.js, Node.js

EDUCATION

DigitalCrafts | Pursing Certificate in Software Engineering- Atlanta, GA Feb 2019-May 2019

♦ Software engineering training program covering a full-stack development including, but not limited to JavaScript, Python, including an emphasis on cutting-edge frameworks like React/Redux and server-side technologies including Node.js, Express, and PostgreSQL.

Clayton State University | B.S. in Psychology & Human Services

December 2010

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT PORTFOLIO

DoTheThing | dothething.chastityduhaney.com

March 2019

- Forming a group of 3 that developed a ticketing system application that works across most screen and web-browsers
- Created full-stack app that used Linux to deploy the application in AWS
- ♦ Used PostgreSQL to create the data base

Movie.io | github.com/cduhanev1/digitalcrafts-movie.io

March 2019

- ◆ Collaborated with a group of 3 that formed a front-end web application using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Implemented 2 remote APIs to pull in the data for the project
- Learned and implemented bootstrap as part of the design

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Delta Airlines Inc. Logistician

Atlanta, GA (October 2017-October 2018)

- Continuously improved processes for warehousing and distribution of aircraft parts
- Prioritized and managed multiple tasks as it pertains to departmental needs

Northside Hospital Patient Access Rep Atlanta, GA (May 2016-December 2017)

- ♦ Upheld all hospital policies and Federal & State guidelines as it pertained to patient's information.
- ♦ Analyzed patient's insurance coverage by appropriately conducting insurance eligibility search, reducing the incidence of claim denial.

Eve Consultants of Atlanta *CSC*

Atlanta, GA (Feb 2015-July 2015)

- Scheduled appropriate appointments for patients according to schedule guidelines.
- Ensured proper inputting of patients' information in a timely and efficient manner as pertains to policy and procedures